Total Experience: 5 Year(s)

Notice Period: 1 Month

ANKUR KATARIA () Featured

Software Engineer seeking roles in Web Development, Application Development, Software Development Life Cycle, Requirement Gathering, Application Testing, Debugging, Incident Management, Process Improvement, Prestashop, Javascript, Linux, MySQL, HTML.



Current Designation: Software Engineer- Web Development

Current Company: Vansun Mediatech Pvt. Ltd.

Current Location: Gurgaon Highest Degree: MBA/PGDM [Advance Computing]

Pref. Location: Chandigarh, Delhi / NCR, Jaipur

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Engineer, Software Development, Application Development, Software Development

Life Cycle, Requirement Gathering, Application Testing, Debugging, Incident Management, Process

Improvement, Prestashop, Javascript, Linux, MySQL, HTML, Ajax.

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Qualified PGDM (Advanced Computing) professional, offering nearly 05 years of rich and extensive experience. Hands-on experience in using various technologies such as STL, PHP, Mongo, Redis, Linux, AWS, Nestjs, Elasticsearch. Efficient in Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) & STLC (Software Test Life Cycle) right from requirement analysis, documentation, coding & testing to the maintenance of proposed applications. Followed the project life cycle methodology defined under the process framework; ensured that customer deadlines were met within project budgets. Communicated with internal/external clients to determine specific requirements and expectations; managed client expectations as an indicator of quality. Developed / reviewed test cases for conducting Unit & System Integration Testing. Displayed skills in designing & developing web applications, and coordinate with the rest of the team working on different layers of the infrastructure

Work Experience

Vansun Mediatech Pvt. Ltd. as Software Engineer- Web Development Aug 2019 to Till Date

Onjections Lab Pvt. Ltd. as Web Developer Dec 2018 to Aug 2019

Nethues Technologies as Software Engineer Feb 2016 to Dec 2018

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Information Technology) from Vaish College of Engineering, MDU, Rohtak in 2014

PG: MBA/PGDM (Advance Computing) from CDAC, Hyderabad in 2015

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Diploma in Instrumentation and Control Engineering

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
PHP, Prestashop, CsCart, STL			3 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
SQL, MYSQL			3 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
Java Script, XML			3 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
HTML, CSS, AJAX, NestJS			3 Year(s) 5 Month(s)
Spring, Struts			
Windows, Linux (Ubuntu), AWS			
Eclipse, NetBeans			
Mongo, Redis			
Codiginator, JQuery			
Custom-MVC			
Database			
GIT			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization